<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>lifeofdan</title>
    <link>https://lifeofdan.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on lifeofdan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>contact@lifeofdan.me (Dan)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>contact@lifeofdan.me (Dan)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://lifeofdan.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hebrews 12:18-29 - A Kingdom That Cannot Be Shaken</title>
      <link>https://lifeofdan.github.io/sermons/hebrews12-akingdomethatcannotbeshaken/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>contact@lifeofdan.me (Dan)</author>
      <guid>https://lifeofdan.github.io/sermons/hebrews12-akingdomethatcannotbeshaken/</guid>
      <description>Hebrews Chapter 12 Summary  Jesus suffered the cross for the goal of our salvation We should endure discipline so that we can become holy In becoming holy we have gained a kingdom that cannot be shaken if we listen to Him The consequences of not doing so are grim. - Our God is a consuming fire.  The book of Hebrews can be quite difficult to understand. It is filled with imagery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music, Roms, Code, Enjoyment</title>
      <link>https://lifeofdan.github.io/posts/music-roms-code-enjoyment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 23:25:57 +1000</pubDate>
      <author>contact@lifeofdan.me (Dan)</author>
      <guid>https://lifeofdan.github.io/posts/music-roms-code-enjoyment/</guid>
      <description>So, this is a post about some of my favorite things at the moment. There is no real point to the post. I just have things that make me happy and I want to share those things with&amp;hellip;no one. Cause no one reads this blog. Or at least I assume no one does. If anyone does, feel free to contact me and say hello. :)
Visual Studio Code So, firstly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew23 WoeToYou Part 4</title>
      <link>https://lifeofdan.github.io/sermons/matthew23-woetoyou-part4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 11:05:34 +1000</pubDate>
      <author>contact@lifeofdan.me (Dan)</author>
      <guid>https://lifeofdan.github.io/sermons/matthew23-woetoyou-part4/</guid>
      <description>This lesson continues the sermon series on the Woes to the Scribes and Pharisees. I had originally thought that this would take maybe two Sundays to go over, but I have really enjoyed diving a little deeper into these verses than I might normally, so I hope that you have found it useful as well.
Before we begin though, let&amp;rsquo;s pray.
Matthew 23:23-28 ESV
 23 “Woe to you, scribes and Pharisees, hypocrites!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew23 WoeToYou Part 3</title>
      <link>https://lifeofdan.github.io/sermons/matthew23-woetoyou-part3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 11:04:51 +1000</pubDate>
      <author>contact@lifeofdan.me (Dan)</author>
      <guid>https://lifeofdan.github.io/sermons/matthew23-woetoyou-part3/</guid>
      <description>The past couple of times we have looked at Matthew 23 we have looked at the hypocrisy of the Scribes and Pharisees. This week we look at their blindness and answer the question, &amp;ldquo;What does Jesus mean when He says that they are blind?&amp;rdquo;
Before we go further though, let&amp;rsquo;s pray.
Matthew 23:16-22
 16 “Woe to you, blind guides, who say, ‘If anyone swears by the temple, it is nothing, but if anyone swears by the gold of the temple, he is bound by his oath.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Setup</title>
      <link>https://lifeofdan.github.io/posts/hugo-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 16:58:49 +1000</pubDate>
      <author>contact@lifeofdan.me (Dan)</author>
      <guid>https://lifeofdan.github.io/posts/hugo-setup/</guid>
      <description>(Image linked from https://themes.gohugo.io/theme/hugo-now/)
Well, it has been one day since I finished the installation of Hugo as my blogging back-end. Wow. It was a bit of a mess. I need to first say that now that everything is up and running, I really like it. Once set up, it makes a lot of sense in the way they have chosen to do things. However, it was a bear to get my head around the setup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Hugo Post</title>
      <link>https://lifeofdan.github.io/posts/my-first-hugo-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 15:52:58 +1000</pubDate>
      <author>contact@lifeofdan.me (Dan)</author>
      <guid>https://lifeofdan.github.io/posts/my-first-hugo-post/</guid>
      <description>This is my first post using Hugo. I heard about it while watching &amp;ldquo;Linux Thursday&amp;rdquo; which is one of the shows on The Lunduke Show. They said it was faster and simpler than Jekyll, which is what I have been using. I had just spend most of the day yesterday setting up my Jekyll site and while I like Jekyll I am wondering if there is something a bit more streamlined.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Professional Development, Selling Me Apples</title>
      <link>https://lifeofdan.github.io/posts/2017-8-25-professional-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>contact@lifeofdan.me (Dan)</author>
      <guid>https://lifeofdan.github.io/posts/2017-8-25-professional-development/</guid>
      <description>So, yesterday I attended a professional development course. For anyone who doesn&amp;rsquo;t know, if you are a teacher in Queensland Australia you are required to attend at least 20 hours of professional development courses. This really isn&amp;rsquo;t that much and is easily achievable. Especially since most schools run some kind of professional development internally. (I&amp;rsquo;m going to call professional development &amp;ldquo;CPD&amp;rdquo; because it stands for &amp;ldquo;continuing professional development&amp;rdquo; from now on to shorten things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Redesign</title>
      <link>https://lifeofdan.github.io/posts/2017-8-24-redesign/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>contact@lifeofdan.me (Dan)</author>
      <guid>https://lifeofdan.github.io/posts/2017-8-24-redesign/</guid>
      <description>It is that time again. I quite liked the old layout of the site. However, I had installed jekyll (the backend of this site) on a different computer and couldn&amp;rsquo;t figure out how to update the thing and it was many versions behind. So, I reinstalled jekyll to my main rig, deleted the old repo and then loaded fresh. (I am a nuke and pave kind of a guy&amp;hellip;I admit it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hard Times</title>
      <link>https://lifeofdan.github.io/posts/2017-8-5-hard-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>contact@lifeofdan.me (Dan)</author>
      <guid>https://lifeofdan.github.io/posts/2017-8-5-hard-times/</guid>
      <description>Hard times.
We all have them. Some hard times are more genuine than others. Dropping your ice-cream cone, while detrimental when you are two years old, is really not as serious as loss of a job, or loss of a loved one, or loss of personal health or safety.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 23 Woe To You Part 2</title>
      <link>https://lifeofdan.github.io/sermons/matthew23-woetoyou-part2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>contact@lifeofdan.me (Dan)</author>
      <guid>https://lifeofdan.github.io/sermons/matthew23-woetoyou-part2/</guid>
      <description>Matthew Chapter 23 is one that is quite famous and well known. I think the reason for that is that hypocrisy is something that we all see and can identify, perhaps daily in our lives or the lives of the people or institutions around us. I think one of the other reasons that this passage is so famous is because there is a passion that comes through the text from the words of Jesus that stirs us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 23 - Woe To You Part 1</title>
      <link>https://lifeofdan.github.io/sermons/matthew23-woetoyou-part1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>contact@lifeofdan.me (Dan)</author>
      <guid>https://lifeofdan.github.io/sermons/matthew23-woetoyou-part1/</guid>
      <description>One of the biggest claims against the church of today is that it is full of hypocrites. Unfortunately, that is many times true. I have heard it said many times that &amp;ldquo;Of course the Church is full of hypocrites!&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;We are imperfect people and we have sin, we recognize it, and that is why we are at church in the first place!&amp;rdquo;
I have oftentimes agreed with this sentiment. I know that I am not perfect and I know that I have sin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMD, Linux, Thoughts on Distros</title>
      <link>https://lifeofdan.github.io/posts/2017-4-24-amd-linux-thoughts-on-distros/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>contact@lifeofdan.me (Dan)</author>
      <guid>https://lifeofdan.github.io/posts/2017-4-24-amd-linux-thoughts-on-distros/</guid>
      <description>Image linked from itsfoss.com
Okay, so my last post was a bit frustrated. I continue to exist in that state of being. :P
This Christmas I built a new computer. Nothing super fancy, but a very nice upgrade for me from a i5 2500k to now running a e3 1230 v5 Xeon processor. I am also running an AMD R9 Fury graphics card. The rationale for the new graphics card and CPU was to run a Windows VM for my gaming with GPU Passthrough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KDE Neon Frustrations...</title>
      <link>https://lifeofdan.github.io/posts/2017-03-16-kde-neon-frustrations/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>contact@lifeofdan.me (Dan)</author>
      <guid>https://lifeofdan.github.io/posts/2017-03-16-kde-neon-frustrations/</guid>
      <description>It has been a month since my last post. I seem to be churning out one of these a month, and that is okay with me. I normally stop doing this after a couple of days. I really like being able to keep track of the work I am doing and being able to access it remotely from a variety of devices. I don&amp;rsquo;t want to make this site something that has ways to comment or anything like that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 John</title>
      <link>https://lifeofdan.github.io/bible-studies/1john/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>contact@lifeofdan.me (Dan)</author>
      <guid>https://lifeofdan.github.io/bible-studies/1john/</guid>
      <description>1 John Introduction to the Book (AATorP) AATorP is Author, Audience, Time or Place
Who is writing the book? Answer: The Apostle John the son of Zebedee, the disciple whom Jesus loved
Who is the book written to? Answer: Christians. It is not specific in exactly who it is written to, but it is obviously written to believers.
For what time and purpose is the book written? Answer: Christian Age.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>the newness has worn off</title>
      <link>https://lifeofdan.github.io/posts/2017-02-16-the-newness-has-worn-off/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>contact@lifeofdan.me (Dan)</author>
      <guid>https://lifeofdan.github.io/posts/2017-02-16-the-newness-has-worn-off/</guid>
      <description>A second post? Whaaaaat! I cannot believe I am about to write the second post on a site that I have created. I really enjoy the process of creating the site and making it work. I generally don&amp;rsquo;t care about actually using it. But, this seems kind of special to me.
I have been working more and more with git. I really like it. I haven&amp;rsquo;t really used the more advanced functions that it offers, but I believe I am learning the basics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let Me Be Overtaken</title>
      <link>https://lifeofdan.github.io/communion-meditations/psalmsch7-let-me-be-overtaken/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>contact@lifeofdan.me (Dan)</author>
      <guid>https://lifeofdan.github.io/communion-meditations/psalmsch7-let-me-be-overtaken/</guid>
      <description>Recently I have begun to listen to the Psalms as I am driving around. I find most of them to be comforting or encouraging. The language is so grand. For example:
Psalms 1:1-2 starts this book out&amp;hellip;
 Blessed is the man who walks not in the counsel of the wicked, nor stands in the way of sinners, nor sits in the seat of scoffers; but his delight is in the law of the Lord, and on his law he meditates day and night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew</title>
      <link>https://lifeofdan.github.io/bible-studies/matthew/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>contact@lifeofdan.me (Dan)</author>
      <guid>https://lifeofdan.github.io/bible-studies/matthew/</guid>
      <description>Matthew Introduction to the Book (AATorP) AATorP is Author, Audience, Time or Place.
Who is writing the book? Answer: The Disciple Matthew
Who is the book written to? Answer: Jewish Christians
For what time and purpose is the book written? Answer: Christian Age. It is written to tell Jewish Christians about Jesus Christ.
Chapter 1 Introduction Has AATorP Changed? Synopsis of Chapter Verses Chapter 2 Introduction Has AATorP Changed? Synopsis of Chapter Verses Chapter 3 Introduction Has AATorP Changed?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not What We Expect (What We Need)</title>
      <link>https://lifeofdan.github.io/communion-meditations/revch5-not-what-we-expect/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>contact@lifeofdan.me (Dan)</author>
      <guid>https://lifeofdan.github.io/communion-meditations/revch5-not-what-we-expect/</guid>
      <description>Revelation is an interesting book. Just making that statement probably fills most of you with worry. You are thinking &amp;ldquo;Oh dear, what is he going to say. What thing is he going to talk about that probably makes no sense whatsoever.&amp;rdquo; None the less, it is an interesting book, that is filled with hope for those who believe.
The scripture I want to look at is:
Revelation 5:1-5 ESV &amp;gt; 5 Then I saw in the right hand of him who was seated on the throne a scroll written within and on the back, sealed with seven seals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lifeofdan site launched</title>
      <link>https://lifeofdan.github.io/posts/2017-01-30-first-post-lifeofdan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>contact@lifeofdan.me (Dan)</author>
      <guid>https://lifeofdan.github.io/posts/2017-01-30-first-post-lifeofdan/</guid>
      <description>Well, I am finally putting up a site that I believe I will maintain. I have put up many sites throughout the years, but they always fall into disarray. This time I actually need this site. I need it to work so that I can work.
I am super excited, and if you are reading this&amp;hellip;don&amp;rsquo;t you have anything better to do?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://lifeofdan.github.io/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>contact@lifeofdan.me (Dan)</author>
      <guid>https://lifeofdan.github.io/page/about/</guid>
      <description>Just your typical Christian, husband, father, teacher, minister, gamer, guitar player, linux enthusiast, computer builder, tech juknie.
I love my family. I like virtually all things technology. I enjoy meeting with my Church. I enjoy all of the students that I teach. I like to play video games and I like learning new things. For example, I am learning about github and jekyll while putting up this website. Too cool. Hobbies are fun.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>