<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Communion on lifeofdan</title>
    <link>https://lifeofdan.github.io/tags/communion/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Communion on lifeofdan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>contact@lifeofdan.me (Dan)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>contact@lifeofdan.me (Dan)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://lifeofdan.github.io/tags/communion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>1 John</title>
      <link>https://lifeofdan.github.io/bible-studies/1john/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>contact@lifeofdan.me (Dan)</author>
      <guid>https://lifeofdan.github.io/bible-studies/1john/</guid>
      <description>1 John Introduction to the Book (AATorP) AATorP is Author, Audience, Time or Place
Who is writing the book? Answer: The Apostle John the son of Zebedee, the disciple whom Jesus loved
Who is the book written to? Answer: Christians. It is not specific in exactly who it is written to, but it is obviously written to believers.
For what time and purpose is the book written? Answer: Christian Age.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let Me Be Overtaken</title>
      <link>https://lifeofdan.github.io/communion-meditations/psalmsch7-let-me-be-overtaken/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>contact@lifeofdan.me (Dan)</author>
      <guid>https://lifeofdan.github.io/communion-meditations/psalmsch7-let-me-be-overtaken/</guid>
      <description>Recently I have begun to listen to the Psalms as I am driving around. I find most of them to be comforting or encouraging. The language is so grand. For example:
Psalms 1:1-2 starts this book out&amp;hellip;
 Blessed is the man who walks not in the counsel of the wicked, nor stands in the way of sinners, nor sits in the seat of scoffers; but his delight is in the law of the Lord, and on his law he meditates day and night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew</title>
      <link>https://lifeofdan.github.io/bible-studies/matthew/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>contact@lifeofdan.me (Dan)</author>
      <guid>https://lifeofdan.github.io/bible-studies/matthew/</guid>
      <description>Matthew Introduction to the Book (AATorP) AATorP is Author, Audience, Time or Place.
Who is writing the book? Answer: The Disciple Matthew
Who is the book written to? Answer: Jewish Christians
For what time and purpose is the book written? Answer: Christian Age. It is written to tell Jewish Christians about Jesus Christ.
Chapter 1 Introduction Has AATorP Changed? Synopsis of Chapter Verses Chapter 2 Introduction Has AATorP Changed? Synopsis of Chapter Verses Chapter 3 Introduction Has AATorP Changed?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not What We Expect (What We Need)</title>
      <link>https://lifeofdan.github.io/communion-meditations/revch5-not-what-we-expect/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>contact@lifeofdan.me (Dan)</author>
      <guid>https://lifeofdan.github.io/communion-meditations/revch5-not-what-we-expect/</guid>
      <description>Revelation is an interesting book. Just making that statement probably fills most of you with worry. You are thinking &amp;ldquo;Oh dear, what is he going to say. What thing is he going to talk about that probably makes no sense whatsoever.&amp;rdquo; None the less, it is an interesting book, that is filled with hope for those who believe.
The scripture I want to look at is:
Revelation 5:1-5 ESV &amp;gt; 5 Then I saw in the right hand of him who was seated on the throne a scroll written within and on the back, sealed with seven seals.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>