<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sermons on lifeofdan</title>
    <link>https://lifeofdan.github.io/tags/sermons/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sermons on lifeofdan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>contact@lifeofdan.me (Dan)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>contact@lifeofdan.me (Dan)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://lifeofdan.github.io/tags/sermons/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hebrews 12:18-29 - A Kingdom That Cannot Be Shaken</title>
      <link>https://lifeofdan.github.io/sermons/hebrews12-akingdomethatcannotbeshaken/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>contact@lifeofdan.me (Dan)</author>
      <guid>https://lifeofdan.github.io/sermons/hebrews12-akingdomethatcannotbeshaken/</guid>
      <description>Hebrews Chapter 12 Summary  Jesus suffered the cross for the goal of our salvation We should endure discipline so that we can become holy In becoming holy we have gained a kingdom that cannot be shaken if we listen to Him The consequences of not doing so are grim. - Our God is a consuming fire.  The book of Hebrews can be quite difficult to understand. It is filled with imagery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew23 WoeToYou Part 4</title>
      <link>https://lifeofdan.github.io/sermons/matthew23-woetoyou-part4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 11:05:34 +1000</pubDate>
      <author>contact@lifeofdan.me (Dan)</author>
      <guid>https://lifeofdan.github.io/sermons/matthew23-woetoyou-part4/</guid>
      <description>This lesson continues the sermon series on the Woes to the Scribes and Pharisees. I had originally thought that this would take maybe two Sundays to go over, but I have really enjoyed diving a little deeper into these verses than I might normally, so I hope that you have found it useful as well.
Before we begin though, let&amp;rsquo;s pray.
Matthew 23:23-28 ESV
 23 “Woe to you, scribes and Pharisees, hypocrites!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew23 WoeToYou Part 3</title>
      <link>https://lifeofdan.github.io/sermons/matthew23-woetoyou-part3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 11:04:51 +1000</pubDate>
      <author>contact@lifeofdan.me (Dan)</author>
      <guid>https://lifeofdan.github.io/sermons/matthew23-woetoyou-part3/</guid>
      <description>The past couple of times we have looked at Matthew 23 we have looked at the hypocrisy of the Scribes and Pharisees. This week we look at their blindness and answer the question, &amp;ldquo;What does Jesus mean when He says that they are blind?&amp;rdquo;
Before we go further though, let&amp;rsquo;s pray.
Matthew 23:16-22
 16 “Woe to you, blind guides, who say, ‘If anyone swears by the temple, it is nothing, but if anyone swears by the gold of the temple, he is bound by his oath.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 23 Woe To You Part 2</title>
      <link>https://lifeofdan.github.io/sermons/matthew23-woetoyou-part2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>contact@lifeofdan.me (Dan)</author>
      <guid>https://lifeofdan.github.io/sermons/matthew23-woetoyou-part2/</guid>
      <description>Matthew Chapter 23 is one that is quite famous and well known. I think the reason for that is that hypocrisy is something that we all see and can identify, perhaps daily in our lives or the lives of the people or institutions around us. I think one of the other reasons that this passage is so famous is because there is a passion that comes through the text from the words of Jesus that stirs us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew 23 - Woe To You Part 1</title>
      <link>https://lifeofdan.github.io/sermons/matthew23-woetoyou-part1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>contact@lifeofdan.me (Dan)</author>
      <guid>https://lifeofdan.github.io/sermons/matthew23-woetoyou-part1/</guid>
      <description>One of the biggest claims against the church of today is that it is full of hypocrites. Unfortunately, that is many times true. I have heard it said many times that &amp;ldquo;Of course the Church is full of hypocrites!&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;We are imperfect people and we have sin, we recognize it, and that is why we are at church in the first place!&amp;rdquo;
I have oftentimes agreed with this sentiment. I know that I am not perfect and I know that I have sin.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>